

Profile

Skillful front-end developer in structuring and developing Single Page Applications (SPA) using front-end JavaScript framework Angular 7. My objectives include producing web applications that work across all platforms with high speed and performance, SEO-friendly, with the meaningful and relevant user experience.

Employment History

Freelance front-end web developer at Mine Mark Foundation, The Hague

May 2019 - Present

- Planning, developing, debugging and deploying the website
- Coding through using front-end technologies HTML, CSS, Bootstrap 4, Typescript, Angular 7
- Storing and fetching the data through Firebase NoSQL server
- Ensuring the website's usability, implementing SEO, web standards (W3C), and cross-browser, cross-platform, and multiple device compatibility
- Collaborating with the web designer for a consistent look throughout all web properties

Freelance wordpress developer at Machine 4u, Uppsala

June 2019 - Present

- Building an e-commerce web app for selling restaurant equipment
- Using Wordpress and Woocommerce
- Customize themes to meet clients' requirements

Education

Degree of Master of Social Science, Uppsala University, Uppsala, Sweden

September 2014 - June 2016

Bachelor's degree in International relations, Azerbijan University of Languages, Baku, Azerbaijan

September 2004 - June 2008

Other Work Experience

Programme Manager, CRRC

September 2018 – December 2018 Baku, Azerbaijan

Coordinating the EU-funded "Peacebuilding through Capacity Enhancement and Civic Engagement" (PeaCE) Programme in Azerbaijan.

Details

The Hague, Netherlands, +31 6 44 939263

gulnar_mammadova@yahoo.co

Links

Linkedin

Github

Portfolio Website

Skills

Python

JavaScript

HTML & CSS

Angular 7

Bootstrap 4

Typescipt

Amazon Web Services

Firebase

Wordpress

Git

SEO

Languages

English

Azerbaijani

Turkish

Russian

Deputy Venue Technology Manager, AISGOC

March 2017 – May 2017 Baku, Azerbaijan

- Ensuring deployment and test of the technology systems to meet requirements
- Supporting in escalation and resolution of technology-related issues
- Preparing venue specific equipment layout drawings and detailed space design for technology spaces

Teacher, Azerbaijan University of Languages

February 2014 – June 2014 Baku, Azerbijan

• Teaching "History of International Relations"

Policy Analyst, Center for Strategic Studies

January 2011 – March 2012 Baku, Azerbaijan

- Producing political analyses and daily briefs
- Organizing conferences and events

Internships

Volunteer at Åland Islands Peace Institute, Mariehamn, Finland

October 2012 - October 2013

- Doing research in the field of conflict resolution and gender equality
- Assisting in youth empowerment and gender equality projects

Courses

PCAP: Programming Fundamentals in Python (Part 1), Python Institute

AWS Fundamentals Going Cloud-Native, Coursera

February 2019

AWS Essentials, Udemy

February 2019

Programming for Everybody (Getting started with Python), Coursera January 2019

Learn Python - Python programming for Beginners from Scratch, Udemy

December 2018

Angular 6 (formerly Angular 2) - The Complete Guide, Udemy $_{\mbox{\scriptsize July 2018}}$

HTML, CSS, and Javascript for Web Developers, Coursera
January 2018

The Complete JavaScript Course: Build a Real-World Project, Udemy

December 2017